Areeb Ullah Ansari

Sales / Customer Service Rep

Positive and upbeat Sales and Customer Service Rep bringing more than 3 years of customer-facing experience in fast-paced settings. Flexible in working in shifts and adaptable to addressing diverse customer needs. Proven history of multi-tasking, and building trust with customers to promote satisfaction, resolve concerns and maintain long-term loyalty.

Contact #: 647.675.5933 Email: auansari@uwaterloo.ca

86 Seagram Drive, Waterloo, Ontario

SKILLS

Price Identification Cleaning and Sanitizing Inventory Stocking

Cash Register Operations Customer Relations Product Knowledge

EDUCATION

Masters of Engineering | University of Waterloo

Artificial Intelligence Jan-2022 - Aug 2023

WORK EXPERIENCE

Customer Service Representative

Popeyes Chicken · Sep 2021 - Jan 2022

- Processed payments by totaling purchases, processing checks, cash, and store
 or other credit and debit cards.
- Counted tills at beginning of shift with start money and balanced and reconciled register, reflecting financial discrepancies, refunds and account deferrals.
- Exchanged and returned items, noting details in company database and placed returned merchandise in bins for restocking.
- Maintained cleanliness and presentation of stock room and production floor.
- Refilled and rotated items on shelves to maintain well-stocked inventory.
- Handled customer complaints and concerns promptly, escalating complex issues to direct supervisor for quick resolution.

Store associate

Ansari and Sons · Oct 2018 - Aug 2021

- Recommended specific products or services by explaining features and benefits which align with the client needs, to both maximize client retention and satisfaction
- Managed inventory to optimize sales, by requestioning from both company and third party warehouses
- Maintained consistent visual merchandising and housekeeping standards which reflected company standards, current products and ongoing promotions.
- Created a welcoming environment by greeting all customers as they walked through the doors
- · Assisted in opening and closing of the store

Sales Associate

Media Idee Jan 2017 - Jul 2017

- Kept clientele informed by notifying them of preferred customer sales and future merchandise of potential interest
- Documented sales by creating or updating customer profile records
- Ensured to be representative of company vision and ensure that company was profitable

AVAILABILITY

- · Full day: Tuesday, Wednesday, Saturday, Sunday
- Evening/Night: Monday, Friday
- · Morning: Thursday